<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.fenlight" name="FenLightAM" provider-name="AnonyMouse" version="2.1.84">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
        <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <license/>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/addon_icons/fenlight_icon_01.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart_01.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.finder" version="7.4.0" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Finder[/COLOR] Skin" provider-name="Newf276">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.finder/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Finder oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Finder بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Finder&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Finder облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Finder per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Finder od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Finder skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Finder Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Finder από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Finder skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Finder skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Finder skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Finder por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Finder por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Finder por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Finder rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Finder azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Finder-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Finder par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Finder, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Finder por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Finder של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Finder presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Finder felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Finder oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Finder-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Finder di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Finderスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Finder 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Finder teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Finder apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Finder skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Finder oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Finder skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Finder por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Finder de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Finder de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Finder от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Finder, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Finder аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Finder autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Finder, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Finder ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Finder โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Finder dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Finder від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Finder của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Finder 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Finder佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Finder is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Finder هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Finder - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Finder е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Finder és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Finder je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Finder er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Finder ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Finder είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Finder is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Finder is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Finder is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Finder es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Finder es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Finder es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Finder on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Finder azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Finder on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Finder est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Finder est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Finder é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Finder היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Finder je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Finder az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Finder adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Finder er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Finder è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">FinderはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Finder는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Finder yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Finder ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Finder er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Finder is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Finder é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Finder é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Finder este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Finder — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Finder je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Finder је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Finder je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Finder är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Finder je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Finder คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Finder Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Finder є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Finder là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Finder 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Finder是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Finder is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Finder هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Finder - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Finder е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Finder és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Finder je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Finder yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Finder er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Finder ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Finder είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Finder is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Finder is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Finder is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Finder es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Finder es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Finder es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Finder on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Finder Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Finder on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Finder est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Finder est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Finder é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Finder היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Finder je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Finder az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Finder adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Finder er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Finder è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">FinderはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Finder는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Finder yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Finder ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Finder er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Finder is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Finder kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Finder é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Finder é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Finder este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Finder — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Finder je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Finder је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Finder je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Finder är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Finder je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Finder เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Finder Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Finder — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Finder là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Finder 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Finder 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.newf" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Repository Newf[/COLOR]" version="1.0" provider-name="newf276">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Repository Newf">
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/newf276/repository/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/newf276/repository/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/newf276/repository/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CocoJoe2411/repository.cocoscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info><checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CocoJoe2411/repository.cocoscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CocoJoe2411/repository.cocoscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
		<dir>
	        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
	        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
	        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/</datadir>
        </dir>
        <dir>
            <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles/master/packages/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles/master/packages/addons.xml.crc</checksum>
            <datadir>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles/archive</datadir>
            <artdir>https://github.com/a4k-openproject/a4kSubtitles/releases/download/v0.0.13</artdir>
        </dir>
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy/</datadir>
        </dir>
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.inputstreamhelper/addons.xml</info>
           	<checksum>https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.inputstreamhelper/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
           	<datadir zip="true">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.inputstreamhelper/</datadir>
        </dir>
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.youtube/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.youtube/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://slyguy.uk/.repo/repository.slyguy.youtube/</datadir>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>repository</summary>
        <description>kodi stuff</description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.fenlight" version="7.4.0" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Fenlight[/COLOR] Skin" provider-name="Newf276">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.fenlight/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Fenlight oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Fenlight بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Fenlight&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Fenlight облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Fenlight per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Fenlight od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Fenlight skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Fenlight Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Fenlight από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Fenlight skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Fenlight skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Fenlight skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Fenlight por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Fenlight por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Fenlight por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Fenlight rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Fenlight azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Fenlight-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Fenlight par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Fenlight, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Fenlight por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Fenlight של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Fenlight presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Fenlight felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Fenlight oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Fenlight-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Fenlight di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Fenlightスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Fenlight 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Fenlight teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Fenlight apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Fenlight skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Fenlight oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Fenlight skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Fenlight por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Fenlight de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Fenlight de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Fenlight от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Fenlight, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Fenlight аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Fenlight autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Fenlight, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Fenlight ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Fenlight โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Fenlight dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Fenlight від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Fenlight của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Fenlight 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Fenlight佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Fenlight is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Fenlight هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Fenlight - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Fenlight е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Fenlight és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Fenlight je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Fenlight er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Fenlight ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Fenlight είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Fenlight es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Fenlight es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Fenlight es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Fenlight on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Fenlight azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Fenlight on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Fenlight est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Fenlight est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Fenlight é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Fenlight היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Fenlight je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Fenlight az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Fenlight adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Fenlight er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Fenlight è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">FenlightはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Fenlight는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Fenlight yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Fenlight ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Fenlight er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Fenlight is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Fenlight é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Fenlight é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Fenlight este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Fenlight — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Fenlight je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Fenlight је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Fenlight je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Fenlight är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Fenlight je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Fenlight คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Fenlight Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Fenlight є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Fenlight là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Fenlight 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Fenlight是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Fenlight is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Fenlight هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Fenlight - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Fenlight е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Fenlight és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Fenlight je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Fenlight yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Fenlight er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Fenlight ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Fenlight είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Fenlight is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Fenlight es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Fenlight es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Fenlight es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Fenlight on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Fenlight Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Fenlight on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Fenlight est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Fenlight est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Fenlight é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Fenlight היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Fenlight je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Fenlight az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Fenlight adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Fenlight er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Fenlight è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">FenlightはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Fenlight는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Fenlight yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Fenlight ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Fenlight er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Fenlight is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Fenlight kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Fenlight é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Fenlight é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Fenlight este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Fenlight — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Fenlight je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Fenlight је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Fenlight je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Fenlight är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Fenlight je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Fenlight เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Fenlight Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Fenlight — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Fenlight là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Fenlight 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Fenlight 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.cbc"
       name="Canadian Broadcasting Corp (CBC)"
       version="8.0.22+matrix.1"
       provider-name="micahg,t1m,smf007,oshanrube,jgaudet">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.5.6"/>
    <import addon="script.module.routing" version="0.2.3+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.unidecode" version="1.1.1+matrix.2"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
	<provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
    <summary lang="en_GB">CBC TV Kodi Plugin</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">View online content from the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language>en</language>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the CBC TV thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=328421</forum>
    <website>https://watch.cbc.ca/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/micahg/plugin.video.cbc</source>
    <news>
      - Fixed Categories, they now display proper content.
    </news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.xumoplay" version="2025.01.06" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Xumo TV[/COLOR]"  provider-name="Newf276">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Xumo Play</summary>
    <description lang="en">Xumo Play is your destination for free LIVE and on-demand streaming channels ranging from sports highlights to fun recipes to music and festival coverage to stand up comedy.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL(v2 or later)</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://play.xumo.com</website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
    <news>Fix for DRM license requirement on some movies</news>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.seren" version="7.4.0" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Seren[/COLOR] Skin" provider-name="Newf276">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.seren/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Seren oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Seren بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Seren&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Seren облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Seren per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Seren od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Seren skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Seren Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Seren από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Seren skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Seren skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Seren skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Seren por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Seren por phil65. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Seren por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Seren rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Seren azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Seren-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Seren par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Seren, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Seren por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Seren של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Seren presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Seren felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Seren oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Seren-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Seren di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Serenスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Seren 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Seren teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Seren apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Seren skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Seren oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Seren skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Seren por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Seren de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Seren de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Seren от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Seren, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Seren аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Seren autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Seren, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Seren ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodno skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Seren โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Seren dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Seren від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Seren của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Seren 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Seren佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Seren is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">Seren هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي الإصدار 17.0 و أعلى. يطمح بأن يكون سهل الاستخدام والفهم لمستخدمين كودي الجدد.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Seren - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi 17.0 і пазнейшых версій. Яна будзе простай і зразумелай для карыстальнікаў, якія не мелі досведу працы з Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Seren е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Seren és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d&apos;entendre i d&apos;utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Seren je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Seren er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Seren ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Seren είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Seren is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Seren is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Seren is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Seren es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Seren es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Seren es la máscara por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Su objetivo es ser fácil de entender y usar para los usuarios nuevos a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Seren on Kodi vaikerüü versioonist 17.0. Kodi esmakasutajatel on rüüd kerge mõista ja kasutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Seren azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی ۱۷٫۰ و بالاتر است. این پوسته تلاش می‌کند درک و استفاده‌اش برای کاربرانی که نخستین بار با کودی کار می‌کنند، ساده باشد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Seren on Kodin oletusulkoasu alkaen versiosta 17.0. Sen on tarkoitus olla uusille Kodi-käyttäjille selkeä ja helppokäyttöinen.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Seren est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Seren est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Seren é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Seren היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Seren je zadana presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Seren az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban. Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Seren adalah skin default untuk Kodi 17.0 dan di atasnya. Ini untuk mudah dipahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna Kodi yang pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Seren er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Seren è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e da usare per chi si avvicina per la prima volta a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">SerenはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Seren는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Seren yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Seren ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Seren er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Seren is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Seren é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Seren é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Seren este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Seren — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0. Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Seren je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Je výsledkom snahy o vzhľad, ktorý bude ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Seren је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Seren je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Seren är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Seren je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Seren คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Seren Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Seren є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Seren là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 17.0 trở lên. Nó dễ dàng cho người dùng Kodi lần đầu tiên hiểu và sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Seren 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Seren是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Seren is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">Seren هو المظهر الافتراضي ل كودي, إزالته قد تسبب بعض المشاكل</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Seren - прадвызначаная абалонка для Kodi. Яе выдаленне можа прывесці да праблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Seren е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Seren és l&apos;aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s&apos;elimina pot causar problemes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Seren je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Seren yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Seren er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Seren ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Seren είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Seren is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Seren is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Seren is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Seren es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Seren es el skin por defecto de Kodi, quitarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Seren es la máscara predeterminada de Kodi, eliminarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Seren on Kodi vaikerüü, selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada probleeme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Seren Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">اسچوری پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی است. ممکن است برداشتنش موجب مشکلاتی شود</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Seren on Kodin oletusulkoasu ja sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Seren est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Seren est l&apos;habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Seren é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Seren היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Seren je zadana presvlaka za Kodi, njegovo uklanjanje može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Seren az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Seren adalah skin default untuk Kodi, menghapusnya dapat menyebabkan masalah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Seren er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Seren è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">SerenはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Seren는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Seren yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Seren ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Seren er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Seren is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Seren kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Seren é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Seren é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Seren este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Seren — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Seren je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Seren је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Seren je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Seren är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Seren je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Seren เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Seren Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Seren — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Seren là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi, loại bỏ nó có thể gây ra sự cố</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Seren 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Seren 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.seren" version="3.0.66" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Seren[/COLOR]" provider-name="Newf276,Nixgates">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.9.910" />
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.27.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
        <import addon="context.seren" version="2.2.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.5.10" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.unidecode" version="1.1.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="8.0.18" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="seren.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Seren - Modular Multi-source Addon</summary>
        <description lang="en">Seren is a modular provider based, cloud service streaming software that is tightly interwoven with Trakt. Seren provides the freedom to view media from a single menu system from service providers of the users choosing. Please Note: This addon requires the use of a compatible cloud service.
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum/>
        <website>https://github.com/nixgates/plugin.video.seren</website>
        <source>https://github.com/nixgates/plugin.video.seren</source>
        <disclaimer lang="en">
            Last updated: December 6, 2024.
            The information contained within the Seren software (the "Service") is for general information purposes
            only.
            The author assumes no responsibility for errors, omissions in the contents on the Service, nor does it
            assume responsibility for any material provided by any external services.
            The use of the Service does not author the user to engage in any kind of illegal, criminal or tortious
            activity through the use of the software, including infringement of any third party intellectual property
            rights (including without limitation copyright, trade marks, patent, trade secrets and confidential
            information), fraud, child pornography, trafficking in obscene material, violation of applicable export
            restrictions, drug dealing, gambling, harassment, stalking, spamming, hacking, sending of viruses or other
            harmful files or illegal posting of computer passwords or computer code.
            The user is responsible for all their activity in connection with the use of the Service and the author
            reserves the right to report any potentially criminal activity to appropriate law enforcement agencies.
            The user must not transmit to or via the Service, any material that may infringe the intellectual property
            rights of any third party, or any defamatory, derogatory or offensive material or publication.
            In no event shall the author of this software be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or
            incidental damages or any damages whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort,
            arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service.
            The author reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modification to the contents on the Service
            at any time without prior notice.
            The author of this software does not warrant that the software is free of viruses or other harmful
            components.
            Seren may contain links to external websites that are not provided or maintained by or in any way affiliated
            with the author.
            Please note that the author does not guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of any
            information on these external websites.
        </disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/images/ico-seren-3.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/images/fanart-seren-3.png</fanart>
            <clearlogo>resources/images/logo-seren-3.png</clearlogo>
            <poster>resources/images/poster-seren-3.png</poster>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>
            Changelog 3.0.66
            [BUG] Resolved Kodi Omega deprecation warnings by migrating cast metadata to InfoTagVideo APIs
            [BUG] Fixed cast normalization to build xbmc.Actor objects and stop setCast runtime exceptions
            [BUG] Normalized unique IDs and resume data to prevent type errors and deprecated property usage
            [BUG] Ensured widget refresh runtime flag resets correctly after triggering refresh
            [BUG] Stopped duplicate episode rows during Trakt sync by keying upserts on show/season/number

            Changelog 3.0.65
            [BUG] Improved SQLite database lock handling
            [BUG] If you skip back to the start and stop playback seren will now stop trakt scrobble and remove playback history
            [BUG] Will no longer use stretched icon for fanart on menu items
            [PERFORMANCE] Will no longer remove trakt bookmark when starting playback
            [PERFORMANCE] Resuming playback will now seek faster
            [PERFORMANCE] Removed unnecessary error when RD magnet doesn't resolve
            [FEATURE] Can limit next up episodes by item limit
            [FEATURE] Added sorting options for watchlist
            [FEATURE] Can now use chapter info to trigger smartplay window
            [FEATURE] Added progress indicators

            Changelog 3.0.62
            [BUG] Optimised RD fix implementation
            [BUG] Improved RD season pack handling
            [BUG] Improved RD download handling when uncached
            [BUG] Improved RD file selection handling when uncached

            Changelog 3.0.61
            [BUG] Fix AD not deleting magnet if not cached

            Changelog 3.0.6
            [BUG] Fix AD Playback

            Changelog 3.0.5
            [BUG] Fix RD playback
            [BUG] Improved 3D Filtering
            [FEATURE] Added option to filer results by internet speed
            [FEATURE] Added 'Cancel' button to smartplay window
            [FEATURE] Added 'Icon Only' scraper display style option
            [FEATURE] Added 'Minimum Percentage Left Before Showing Dialog option' for smartplay window
            [FEATURE] Added option to hide resolver window when attempting to play
            [FEATURE] Added 60 FPS filter

            Changelog 3.0.1
            [FEATURE] Handle Kodi database version for Omega 21
            [PERFORMANCE] Compressed icons from 3.53 MB to 1.34 (Removed)
            [FEATURE] Update background color to Black for 3.0.1 (Removed)

            Changelog 3.0.0
            [PERFORMANCE] Drop support for Python 2.x (Kodi Leia and below)
            [PERFORMANCE] Optimize codebase for Python 3.x (Kodi Matrix and above)
            [PERFORMANCE] Improvements to Smart Play
            [PERFORMANCE] Improve playlist creation
            [PERFORMANCE] Don't use strptime
            [PERFORMANCE] Small perf improvement to supported file type checks
            [PERFORMANCE] Optimize from_widget detection
            [PERFORMANCE] Optimize movie release date handling
            [PERFORMANCE] Use cache for pull_all if not page 1 and ignore_cache = True
            [FEATURE] Introduce support for direct sources
            [FEATURE] Better support for adaptive sources
            [FEATURE] Better passing of movie aliases to providers
            [FEATURE] Smoother resolver flow
            [FEATURE] Convert add-on settings to new format
            [FEATURE] Add AV1 filter
            [FEATURE] Rework alias passing to scrapers
            [FEATURE] Better identification of WEB and BLURAY sources
            [FEATURE] Support clearlogo from TMDB
            [FEATURE] Prioritize Trakt airdate metadata
            [FEATURE] Update Seren logo for 3.0.0
            [FEATURE] Icons for all menus
            [FEATURE] Support package and provider icons
            [FEATURE] Add Hebrew localizations
            [FEATURE] Update pytz to 2022.7
            [BUG] Improve Player resiliency and error handling (re-factor)
            [BUG] Fix Multiple issues with player up next popup and track watched reported
            [BUG] Fix Task Done error (re-write Threadpool)
            [BUG] Fix Smartplay not working after 2nd episode watched
            [BUG] Improve Database handling and Foreign Key references (DB schema refactor)
            [BUG] Increase RD timeout
            [BUG] Fix Trakt bookmark handling
            [BUG] Fix TVDB Normalization error
            [BUG] Fix Most TV Show Episodes/Seasons don't have certification (MPAA)
            [BUG] Fix Awake from sleep sometimes misses plugin calls
            [BUG] Fix Seren not playing some cached files from Premiumize
            [BUG] Fix sort_select tries to read invalid settings
            [BUG] Fix Local time conversion not happening for movies releases
            [BUG] Fix Clear logo overlap on getSources window
            [BUG] Fix Widgets Disappear on Error
            [BUG] Fix two bugs with Trakt watched/unwatched actions
            [BUG] Fix missing seeds count when Manual Caching
            [BUG] Fix typo in German localizations
            [BUG] Remove rogue \ in translations

            Changelog 2.2.4
            [BUG] Fix bugs related to foreign key constraints

            Changelog 2.2.3
            [BUG] Fix Trakt Scrobbling and Playing Next
            [FEATURE] Update pytz to 2022.6

            Changelog 2.2.2
            [BUG] Trakt scrobbling hitting rate limiter
            [BUG] Improve onWake and sleeping service calls
            [FEATURE] Update pytz to 2022.5
            [FEATURE] Fixed 'info_text' item property for themes

            Changelog 2.2.1
            [BUG] Error on fresh install from update news
            [BUG] Discover TV Shows Genre multi-select not working
            [PERFORMANCE] Limit search to title and aliases only

            Changelog 2.2.0
            [FEATURE] Complete refactor of source sorting
            [FEATURE] Add enhanced filtering options
            [FEATURE] Improve release title info detection
            [FEATURE] Improved source statistics, filtering and pretermination
            [FEATURE] Updated default seren skin
            [FEATURE] Window class refactors
            [FEATURE] Add adaptive source selection when smartplaying
            [FEATURE] "Original" for TMDB for High artwork size
            [FEATURE] Allow deleting single search terms from search history
            [FEATURE] Base List Types for Genres default setting switch
            [FEATURE] Add trakt user blocked notification.
            [FEATURE] Auto clean torrent cache
            [FEATURE] Re-open settings at correct place
            [FEATURE] Add verbiage in our news function about source sorting changes
            [FEATURE] Update pytz to 2022.1
            [FEATURE] Add Kodi 20 Alpha1 Videodb support (Note: Kodi 20 is not officially supported yet)
            [PERFORMANCE] Lazy load dependencies and optimize imports
            [PERFORMANCE] Improve performance of pre-emptive termination checks
            [PERFORMANCE] Improve performance of source sorting and cloud scrapers
            [PERFORMANCE] Improve performance of source filtering
            [PERFORMANCE] Optimize TVDB
            [PERFORMANCE] Optimise year generation code for menus
            [BUG] Fix background updating of shows
            [BUG] List cache on first boot for widgets broken
            [BUG] Marking an episode as unwatched via CM does not remove last_watched_at in DB
            [BUG] Marking show watched/unwatched shouldn't affect specials
            [BUG] Handle error response from OMDb
            [BUG] Increase read timeout for trakt when milling all seasons
            [BUG] Try close session for trakt.tv
            [BUG] Double widget refresh can occur when playback ends and trakt manager
            [BUG] Trakt Manager --> Hide Show
            [BUG] Duplicate episodes when trakt_id changes
            [BUG] Tvdb fallback is not working as it should
            [BUG] TMDB Show meta never up to par
            [BUG] TMDB air_dates have no time component
            [BUG] Fix TMDB Rate limiting handler
            [BUG] My Lists don't pull all lists
            [BUG] Duplicate my lists lists when no_paging enabled
            [BUG] Remove a4kSubtitles Integration
            [BUG] IndexError from sort_sources
            [BUG] TVDB errors when there is no item in the iterator
            [BUG] Shuffle Play not working when "Flatten Season Episodes" enabled
            [BUG] Seren not passing aliases to a4kScrapers for movies
            [BUG] Cloud Scrapers don't find episodes that include year after title
            [BUG] Change NoPlayableSourcesExcetion to log at info level
            [BUG] Fix getSources progress calculation
            [BUG] Fixup adaptive handling since the source sorting and statistic changes
            [BUG] Limit flip multiple providers to the current package
            [BUG] Ensure we have a valid integer value for torrent seeds
            [BUG] Fix Premiumize transfer progress values
            [BUG] Return gracefully when we have no valid zipfile from install package
            [BUG] Handles source sizes in KB
            [BUG] Fix focus issues on windows
            [BUG] Fix provider module import issues
            [BUG] Improve handling of Kodi object cleanup

            Changelog 2.1.9
            Fix PM Application Authorization
            Fix show pack retrieval in torrent cache
            Fix a4kSubtitles import path for case sensitive filesystems
            Use addon id in setting cache prefix for kodi window properties
            Fix focus broken in provider window with no providers

            Changelog 2.1.8
            Fix prescrape cache result being ignored
            Fix get_sources to return all relevant torrent hashes from torrent cache
            Some minor cache performance improvements

            Changelog 2.1.7
            Fix MyFiles listings for all FileWalkers
            Fix Rescrape item should overwrite torrent cache
            Added info meta up to par check in fallback logic
            Fix playback history normalization needed for Quick Resume context menu bug
            Fix reset playback progress for shows/seasons/episodes
            Handle Cloudflare 530 error for Trakt
            Fix Premiumize.me space_used now returns value in TB
            Handle bugs in Premiumize.me API for list files gracefully.

            Changelog 2.1.6
            Work around Sqlite on Leia under Windows does not support boolean named values
            Ensure we fetch all pages for syncing ratings and ignore cache for bookmark/hidden sync
            Fix collections.Mapping import for Python >= 3.3

            Changelog 2.1.5
            Workaround trakt shitty season data
            Added trakt list sort types for Watched, Collected and My Rating
            Fix trakt season milling for updated shows
            Fix mill_if_needed queries for seasons and episodes
            Use cache for first load of widgets for trakt lists
            Force a cache clear on release version changes
            Update seasons statistics again, with even more fallbacks
            Ensure we clean up AD/RD cloudfiles if we can't identify the file to play
            Fixed typo in url for widget refresh from activities sync
            Allow widget refresh while playing for foreground tasks
            Fix air dates not always showed correctly for shows/seasons
            Fix tzlocal call to pytz.tzinfo.build_tzinfo and update pytz to 2021.3
            Hide trakt auth option if we are already authed
            Change icons to transparent background
            Use an empty content type value for menu containers
            Added 'an' to the list of excluded sort tokens
            Update Dutch translations
            Update French translations
            Add Polish translations

            Changelog 2.1.4
            Genre and Next Page icons
            Improve widget refresh logic
            Update show/season statistics after reinserting from updated meta
            Perform trakt sync on system resume
            Support kodi standard addon localisations
            Fix downloads
            Fix hide shows from episodes/season items
            Add "Auto-Delete Torrents" for AD
            Fix RD torrents not auto-deleting
            Fix broken cache cleaning
            Don't use show OMDB data for seasons
            Remove update checker
            Localize custom windows
            Use show ids for setUniqueIDs
            Always mill specials
            Optimise TVDB threading
            Optimise filter_dictionary and safe_dict_get
            Increase requests connection pool size
            Don't use dict.keys() when unnecessary
            Some minor fixes and optimisations to tools and globals
            Minor performance improvement to the sqlite row factory
            Optimise TZ initialisation
            Debounce onSettingsChanged callback in SerenMonitor
            Added database indices to episodes, movies, hidden and bookmarks tables

            Changelog 2.1.3
            Workaround Kodi's lack of multi-process settings management
            Fix Trakt updated endpoints now only support 30 days from "now"
            Fix call to get_url in RD account status check and enhanced PM and AD account status checks
            Fix Trakt IDs being sent wrong to windows

            Changelog 2.1.2
            Fix RD auth when there are existing values in settings.xml
            Get debrid premium status immediately after auth and improve values/handling
            Make Trakt auth for widget loads needing auth to wait for auth
            Ensure all trakt API instances always get latest auth tokens
            Fix Trakt revoke auth issues that led to bad values in settings.xml
            Don't wipe user data in trakt sync db on trakt revoke auth unless next authed user is different
            Fix clipboard copy to work on Linux under Matrix and and add MacOS support
            Fix season milling requires update check
            Fix adding unaired items to watchlist from search when hide unaired is enabled
            Fix eternal trakt IDs for trakt addon ratings/scrobbling for episodes
            Fix trakt list sorting direction for rank sorting
            Don't cache personal trakt lists
            Reorder code path in GlobalLock to avoid rare race condition
            Fix Long life service manager does not exit when kodi requests it to
            Change InputStream Helper dependency to optional
            Gracefully handle bad dates in OMDB indexer
            Improved settings cache thread locking
            Handle None/empty values better in settings cache
            VACCUM during DB rebuild (reclaim disk space)

            Changelog 2.1.1
            Fix RD losing auth issue
            Improve OAUTH refresh flow edge case coverage for Trakt and TVDB
            Re-implement retry on db lock during sql execution
            Fix an issue with GlobalLock run_once exiting too early
            Fix several shows views on demand insertion of missing data
            Fix movies genres on demand insertion of missing data
            Update season episode count after episode milling (fixes seasons showing incorrectly as watched)
            Fix minimum size filter

            Changelog 2.1.0
            Major re-work of metadata updates and merging
            Fix air dates not being updated
            Fix missing artwork not being updated
            Fix meta data merging
            Improved meta data fallback processing
            Improve global and sync locks, reduce thread locking
            Improve caching code to reduce required requests.
            Additional caching for metadata indexer endpoints
            Improve database handling code
            Improve timezone detection fallback handling
            Make Seren python version agnostic
            Implemented a true settings cache
            Brought back test windows feature for skin developers
            Moved to kodi module version of unidecode
            Updated pytz to latest release
            Fix mysql Kodi database support under Leia
            Removed youtube dependency
            Workaround for type error in CacheAssist quality filter
            Fix resolver window error when no sources found
            Remove argv usage from SmartPlay
            Reworked forced widget refresh approach
            Logging cleanup

            Changelog 2.0.19
            Fix handling of unicode in URLs, TV Networks and Searching issues on Leia
            Fix TV show years
            Fix PM CacheAssist status updates
            Only try to auto-cache if auto-cache is actually enabled
            Change default threadpool size and provide user settings
            Increase timeout configuration setting maximum permitted value
            Make pre-scrape respect new maximum value for timeout
            Change approach for deaccenting clean_title and transliterate actor names
            During prescrape, don't pop up the too restrictive filters window and just use unfiltered list for sorting
            Fix Kodi Bookmark Clearing with MySQL DB support
            Temporarily disable totaltime progress indicators as they break our resume on Matrix
            Fix TVDB session issues
            Fix XBOX Database Issues
            Fix database pickling issues
            Fix Kodi crashes in Leia
            Fix Kodi crashes in Matrix (with exception of reuselanguageinvoker enabled when stopping playback combined with widgets)
            Change default value of reuselanguageinvoker to False and force use addon provided value on upgrade
            Ensure we release all Kodi objects to prevent memory leaks and crashes
            Ensure we close all requests sessions to prevent memory leaks
            Workaround occasional python bug with strptime in lambda functions
            Made Kodi version detection algorithm more resilient and cover pre-release versions
            Logging enhancements
            Added Arabic translations

            Changelog 2.0.18
            Fix the thread pool issues
            Added logic to push down the country_origin to be used by the scrapers
            Original title swap now only occurs for display, use unicode everywhere
            Fixed normalization function retuning unnormalized values
            Fix for genre multi-select always showing same items
            Fixed local TZ conversion for dates in Upcoming, Source Select and OSD
            Real Debrid use status_codes to determine what are good requests
            Make sure we have all parts for the calculation of the bookmarks
            Added regex to parse semver out of version label
            Re-implemented update checker that will work regardless of repo changes

            Changelog 2.0.17:
            Fix for shows search and TVDB empty data
            Fix handling of timestamp creation to be UTC compliant
            Fix timezone code taking unix path on Windows
            Added a fall through for android getprop timezone detection
            Handle invalid dates from metadata indexer when obtaining year value.
            Fix Matrix UI spins on closing download manager
            Add check for invalid list position in download manager returned by an empty list
            Fix isFolder bool for download manager
            Fix resume progress indicators
            Calculate resumetime at bookmark insert for movies
            Add support for clearing bookmarks on Matrix
            Fix view_type has no attribute isdigit bug
            Ensure studio info value in seasons/episodes
            Add provider package version information to existing logging item
            Handle removal of legacy provider meta file both on uninstall and upgrade
            Replaced seekTime with execute of BigSkipForward
            Fix Simplejson decode error not caught bug
            Handle exception instances from a4ksubtitles
            Fix pagination for genre multi-select
            Fix paging of Finish Watching has same items bug
            Fixed show pack suffixes and checking of 1x1 episode naming
            Updated missing codes and added it-IT, fr-FR and ar-SA translations
            Update Danish language strings

            Changelog 2.0.16:
            Fix addon update check
            Fix trakt module attempting to refresh when not authorised

            Changelog 2.0.15:
            Fixed python depend

            Changelog 2.0.14:
            Fixed scraping issue if title is not present at IMDB
            Added workarounds for syncing trakt database on xbox
            Fixed Trending/Popular Trakt lists repeating
            Seperated sort and pagination setting for Trakt collection
            Applied sort and pagination settings for collection to unfinished shows in collection
            Re-worked date handling to use UTC for all internal uses and convert to local on display
            Fixed pagination on recently watched shows menu
            Fixed source sorting issue for py3
            Fixed race condition in pre-term for py3
            File size now displayed on resolver dialog
            Updated some dutch translations
            Fixed hosters not being handled correctly at scrape
            Fix reuselanguageinvoker default
            Fixed background sync attempting to run when no Trakt auth present

            Changelog 2.0.13
            Fixed settings not sticking when using reuselanguageinvoker
            Fixed reuselanguageinvoke status not sticking after toggling
            Reuselangugageinvoker state now forced on startup
            Reduced Trakt retries on server failures
            Increased backoff timeout for retries
            Fixed playback for special episodes failing
            Eased timeout issues for bookmarks
            Fixed non-direct, non-debrid hosters appearing in source select
            Fix spanish translation file name
            Fixed title sorting for lists with articles
            Fixed paging on new shows

            Changelog 2.0.12
            Fix for source select, tested on 4 skins

            Changelog 2.0.11
            Take preventative measures to reduce overloading Trakt servers
            Increase local show/season statistic refreshing
            Fixed cloud source sorting
            Fixed HEVC source sorting
            New shows api call now pulls english and local language from Trakt
            Modified database commit method to allow for xbox support
            Reformat source select screen again to allow better filename displaying
            Fixed next button showing on next up menu
            Removed pycryptodome dependency, this will need to be requested on a per provider basis
            Fixed pre-term
            Fixed empty search results raising exception
            Fixed auto episode resuming
            Fixed superficial exceptions in play dialogs
            Updated danish language strings

            Changelog 2.0.10
            Fixed issue with milling seasons to often
            Added checks when attempting to cache magnet
            Fixed tvshows new
            Fetching of RD account details after auth fixed
            Fixed spanish translation folder name
            Reformat of source select to allow larger file name sizes
            Fixed race condition in ThreadPool
            Added fallback for text color if skin color could not be inherited
            Add legacy param support for smart play playlist creation
            Fix hide the hiding of unaired episodes from non mixed episode lists
            Removed default action setting until a appropriate workaround for kodi setting is achieved
            Wrapped player interactions with Trakt API with Try/Excepts to allow network failures
            Added fallback method if no thumb art is available
            Added temporary workaround for ratings issue in add_directory_items
            Fixed keep-alive in player module. (Fixes dialogs, playlist creation, marking as watched if not caused by network failure)
            Allowed exceptions in cache check to allow for debrid providers who are offline
            Replaced ok dialogs for connection issues with notifications


            Changelog 2.0.9:
            Fixed RD cloud scraping
            Fixed issue if all providers were disabled scraping would run as if all were enabled
            Fixed smartplay and legacy paramas support
            Fixed bug causing failure when checking art from TMDB
            Fixed user lists menus
            Added spanish translation
            Fixed backing out from menu when opened from widget (having to backout multiple times)
            Fixed season watch markers
            Fixed hidden_items handling with New Shows menu

            Changelog 2.0.8:
            Temporary Workaround for trakt items not providing trakt_id
            Better RD episode resolving
            Better episode identification during resolving
            Catch WindowsError exception when handling skins
            Fix text highlight selection
            Cool down background service on failure

            Changelog 2.0.7:
            Fixed All debrid torrent resolving
            Fixed movie resuming
            Fixed issue with limited providers running at scrape
            Fixed AD re-auth
            Changes to attempt to fix XBOX support and ascii issues with timezones
            Fixed unaired episodes showing blank
            Fixed AD User info fetching
            Fixed ghost providers
            Fixed TypeError with pre-termination

            Changelog 2.0.6:
            Create Skins directory if missing
            Allow failure in pre-term until investigated

            Changelog 2.0.5:
            Allow more failures that will require to be investigated further in the future

            Changelog 2.0.4:
            Safe get release title when cloud scraping
            Allow and log failures in maintenance process

            Changelog 2.0.3:
            Added default value of None for skin color when attempting to pull color from user's skin

            Changelog 2.0.2:
            Force table re-fresh is sync database fails to rebuild when updating

            Changelog 2.0.1:
            Fix last_meta_update value to reflect new Seren version

            Changleog 2.0.0:

            Added Download Manager
            Complete re-write of Trakt Sync Database
            Metadata handler introduced and complete re-write of handling of metadata
            Settings that modify metadata can now be changed on the fly and do not require a rebuild
            Users can now manually resolve a file from the source select screen
            Users can now manually cache a specific source from the source select screen
            Complete re-write of menu handling
            Introduced globals module to handle global variables for interpreter
            Implement re-use language invoker setting from Kodi
            Pre-emptive termination now disabled for background Pre-scrapes and timeout set to max for background scrapes
            New artwork and custom dialogs
            Metadata now upadted on the fly when updated item encountered from Trakt
            Next Up menu now populated from local database
            Sync has been fleshed out to include even more meta data during cycle
            Failures to auto resolve now prompt user in case they wish to manually interrupt
            Items are now able to supply multiple images for any given type for skins that make use of it
            Support for Python 3
            Global thread lock now implemented for required methods (prevents multiple syncs occuring at once and other locks)
            InputStreamAdaptive support
            Providers now have the abiity to implement settings
            Provider packages can now elect to make use of their own background services
            Provider packages can now offer images for each provider
            Cache and Sync database items are now pickled
            Complete re-write of resovler module and consolidated code
            Kodi 19 support
            All Debrid implementation now fully featured
            Sources can now be sorted by filesize low to high for users that wish to do so
            Forcing widget refresh after playback now optional
            Zip manager implemented for handling of zip files
            Skin Manager rework
            Automated resolving now more reliable
            OMDB API implemented
            Feedback provided at scrape if no providers are found
            Feedback provided at scrape if no debrid providers are setup
            Debrid account status now visible from Seren settings
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="context.seren" version="3.0.2" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Seren[/COLOR] - Context Menu" provider-name="Newf276,Nixgates">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="17.9.910" />
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<item library="context.py" args="quickRresume">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30000]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.quickResume)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="shuffle">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30001]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.shuffle)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="playFromRandomPoint">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30002]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.playFromRandomPoint)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="rescrape">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30003]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.rescrape)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="rescrape_ss">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30010]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.rescrape_ss)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="sourceSelect">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30004]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.sourceSelect)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="findSimilar">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30005]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.findSimilar)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="browseShow">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30006]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.browseShow)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,season)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="browseSeason">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30007]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.browseSeason)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context.py" args="traktManager">
				<label>$ADDON[context.seren 30008]</label>
				<visible>String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(context.seren.traktManager)) + String.StartsWith(ListItem.path,plugin://plugin.video.seren/)+[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,season)|String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
			</item>
		</menu>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Seren - Global Context Menu Items</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Seren - Algemene contextmenu-items</summary>
		<description lang="en">Adds Context Menu items for Seren menu items throughout Kodi</description>
		<description lang="nl">Voegt contextmenu-items toe voor Seren-menu-items in Kodi</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website></website>
		<source></source>
		<disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/images/ico-seren-3.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart-seren-3.jpg</fanart>
			<clearlogo>resources/images/logo-seren-3.png</clearlogo>
			<poster>resources/images/poster-seren-3.png</poster>
		</assets>
		<news>
			Changelog 3.0.2
			Compressed icons from 3.53 MB to 1.34
			Update background color to Black

			Changelog 3.0.1
			Fix Shuffle play copy pasta mix up
			Resolve settings not showing in Kodi

			Changelog 3.0.0
			Re-write of context menu addon, supporting py3 only (Matrix and above)
			Update icons to match Seren 3.0.0 release
			Update language support set to match Seren (add auto-translated Hebrew)

			Changelog 2.2.0
			Added "Rescrape and Source Select" context menu item.

			Changelog 2.1.2
			Added Polish translation

			Changelog 2.1.1:
			Implemented a workaround for broken future.backports module method (fixes Leia issues)

			Changelog 2.1.0:
			Refactored code to modern standards
			Use backported URL lib for py2 to ensure unicode compatibility
			Extracted out common functions and reused
			Add settings to enable/disable individual items
			Add more localizations
			Add GitHub issue templates

			Changelog 2.0.2:
			Make python version agnostic

			Changelog 2.0.1:
			Fixed addon icons/fanart

			Changelog 2.0.0:
			Rework for Seren 2.0
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.speedtester" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Speed[/COLOR] Tester" version="14.1.3+matrix.1" provider-name="Newf276, Dr0idGuy, dagwieers">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="resources/lib/addon_entry.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Test your Internet bandwidth</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">This add-on tests your Internet bandwith and reports both download and upload speeds and latency from within Kodi. Use this if you are experiencing streaming issues and you suspect your network to be the cause.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Speed Tester is powered by speedtest.net</disclaimer>
    <language>en</language>
    <license>Apache-2.0</license>
    <source>https://newf276.github.io</source>
        <assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.audio.iheart"
       name="[COLOR dodgerblue]iHeart[/COLOR] Radio"
       version="2.0.2"
       provider-name="newf276">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0+matrix.1"/>
    <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.6.1.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>audio</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_US">Live radio over the internet</summary>
    <description lang="en_US">
    Listen to more than 1,500 live radio stations from coast-to-coast including pop, country, urban, rock, talk, and college.[CR]
    Browse radio stations by music genre and location.[CR]
    Read more: http://news.iheart.com/about/
    </description>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.finder" name="Finder" provider-name="Newf276,AnonyMouse" version="7.1.82">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/finder.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
        <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <license/>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/addon_icons/finder_icon_01.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/finder_fanart_01.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.kodi.apk" name="[COLOR dodgerblue]Newf's[/COLOR]Kodi APK Installer" version="1.0.1" provider-name="Newf276">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.3.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot02.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot03.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot04.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Download and Install Kodi packages.</summary>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
